Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar.
As friends, you all know.
Well friends, I am selected here in ICICI Bank.
But brother, what I am going to tell you in today's video is that
HDFC Bank has
tied up with NIT and has
launched a course here.  S Banker's
program.  Friends,
after completing this course here, you are
directly
given the post of Assistant Manager.  That too friends, here
inside HDFC Bank.  If brother, you complete that,
you complete that course.  The
45-day course has to be completed by going to NIT.
You have to stay there only.  Everything remains free.
Everything residential, everything free.  Your
food, accommodation, everything is free.  There,
everything is
given to you free of cost from the NIT side.  There are some fees
etc. for this which you have to provide.
You can also pay it monthly here.
You can also pay it in installments.
You
can pay it all at once.  Your training program here is going to be of 45 days.
Brother, if you complete this then you are
directly given the post of Assistant Manager here.
HDFC Directly's Ace Banker Program puts you on the roll here.
You get a job here directly.
If brother, you complete that course
directly.  Pan India friends,
you can get it anywhere or here at all, do
not think that you will get it
in our hometown.  This will not happen at all.
Brother friends, you can get it anywhere in pan India,
when your offer letter comes to you here,
its offer letter comes here, as soon as you
join, as soon as you go to the NIT site, as soon as you go to the
NIT university,
an offer letter will be given to you before that, it will be
clearly mentioned in it
that you can be given a location anywhere in pan India.
If you are
interested brother, then you have to
fill it up here and revert it.
Brother, here many people have a doubt
that can we directly
become an assistant manager by doing this program?  Can we
program this and get operations in here
?  Brother,
can we do this program here in Hindi
?  I keep getting a lot of
messages etc.  I keep getting a lot of
DMs etc.  Comments
also keep coming.  So friends,
after watching today's video,
all your doubts are going to be cleared.
So friends, please like the video here and
subscribe to the channel.
Here friends, without wasting time let's
start the video.  Brother, friends, we are talking about the
S Banker program
which is done here from the NIT site.  There
is NIT University
in Neemrana, friends, you have to go
there and complete its 45-day training
program.  Before that,
friends, you have to complete its joining process.
Friends, in the first step, you have to pay a fee of ₹500
here.
After that, an assessment test is
taken from you here.  If brother,
you clear the assessment test.  60%
friends, its
passing marks have been kept here.  If brother,
you complete 60% in the test here.
After that you have your interview.
The interview will be online only.  Everything will be
online.  Friends, you do
not need to go anywhere.  Here AI will
interview you.
Your online test will be conducted through AI only and
after completing it, you have to
deposit ₹10,000 here.
You have to do that here brother.  As soon as you
deposit ₹10,000 your seat gets
confirmed.  If brother, you get a
confirmation mail then you will 100% be
sent there or here.  You will receive the
offer letter etc.  Brother, if you are
not able to complete it here for the first
time, then you get only one attempt here.
After that, if
you are not selected then
you will have to wait for 6 months to
give this test again.  As
friends, I have
already told this in many videos here.
I have already given it here by doing the S Bank program
and I have also qualified for it.
I have
also uploaded its video on my YouTube channel.  Whatever
tests I got,
I have uploaded their As It Is videos on my YouTube channel.
Friends, you
can go here and check out once about the test of S Banker program and see
what kind of
pattern it comes in.  What type of
online test do you have to give here?  All those
friends, you are going to get a similar pattern here.
If brother, you want to give it, then
brother, some people had a doubt that this
program, which is the S Banker program, can
we give it in Hindi, so
brother, many people are thinking whether
we can give it in Hindi, so brother, let me
tell you, this will not happen at all,
you should have 100% proper English here,
it is not that you are
speaking in Hindi, you are talking in Hindi,
this will not work at all, your
interview will also be in English,
your assessment test will also be
in English and whichever university
you go to, you will be taught in English there also.
Whatever communication takes place,
it will be in English only.
Everything will be told to you in English only.
If your English is weak then
definitely do not enroll here
because you are going to be rejected.
You will be rejected 100%.  In what way,
if you clear the test, then
brother, when your interview will take place, face
to face interview in NIT, then
brother, you will be rejected there.
There also, when you
complete 45 days of training,
your test is taken there also.  If
brother, you are not able to complete that test also, then the
₹10,000 that you have here will be returned to you.
Otherwise your seat is cancelled here.
Not at all for Hindi speaking people.
This program should be 100% your English.
Yes, it is that a little can go a long way.
If brother, your English is a little weak then
you can go ahead.
Otherwise, if brother, you know proper Hindi and do
not know even a few words of English, then
brother, you should
not think about this course at all.  Ok?   This
course is definitely not for you.  Because
brother, I have already given it here that
100% your conversation takes place in English.
Communication takes place in English.
Everything here is given to you in English only.
Brother, if you know English then
you should enroll in this course here.   Don't do it otherwise.
Now friends, many
people say that in this you will get
operations or sales.  So
brother, let me tell you.  Brother, you can
also get your operation done in this.
You can also get sales in this.  Even if you are
given operations, brother, you should be
given 100% sales in it because brother, the
sales you make here are 60 to 70% of
your sales.  30% friends, your
operations are here.  Brother, even if you are made to
sit on the cashier etc. or
on KYC, you will still have to do
100% sales.
You will be given some target there.  Your
branch manager will give you the target.
You will have to complete that sale.  So do
n't think at all that you will get a cell
or an operation here.  You do
n't have to do anything on operations.  It has to be done 100%.
You have to do sales.  Now brother, some
people are asking me that brother, is it beneficial for
us to take this course by spending ₹5 lakh
?  So brother, let me tell you for them.
Absolutely yes, grade one job
is available.  You get grade one.
Friends,
you are given the post of Assistant Manager directly.
In HDFC Bank you are given direct post.
100% worth ₹1.5 lakh.  There
is no problem.  For ₹1 lakh, you have to pay a fee of something like ₹170 or something like
₹75,000.
You can pay it in installments.
You can pay it any way you want.   There
is no problem.  Rest brother is
worth it.  There is no problem.
Brother, many people had this doubt.  I have
told you this and have told you clearly.
Hindi speaking people should listen especially.   It will
not work at all in Hindi.   Of
course, you will need 100% proficiency in English.
Ok?  Rest of the friends,
I have told you about this course.  The
rest is your choice.  If you want to enroll in it, you can
enroll.  Rest of
its batches are about to start here.
You can enroll in it if you want to do it brother.
You should watch that video to see
what kind of pattern is seen in it.
You should watch the
video once.  I will give you the link in the description box.
You can check out once.
Rest of the friends, I have
told you about the course in this video.
I hope you liked this video very much.  If you liked the
video, please give it a like.
Friends, if you have not yet subscribed to this channel, then
brother,
go quickly and subscribe to this channel.
See you in the next video.  Till then
take care.